I have an announcement to make today.
People?
Why?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's nice to meet you.
Yay!
Yay.
Notification.
You're notified.
Oh, my God.
Good morning
Good morning. Good morning.
I'm here today to offer you a job.
What? Thank you very much.
Mr. Miyagi and Steve and I.
Ehhhh!
Oh my God!
We're going to have a collaboration event with Mr. Miyagi and us, Steve.
Ehhhh!
Oh no!
I'm so excited!
We would like you to prepare this item.
We would love to have this item available.
Thank you very much.
Let's start with the T-shirts.
Julian!
I think this is the product we want to push the most.
Here it is.
Yay!
Amazing.
Yay.
That's great.
Oh, my gosh. amazing (e.g. of strength)
amazing
That's great.
Yay!
Thank you so much.
That's great! The content?
The content is good.
Yes, it is. I would like to deliver these products.
Don't you like it?
Yes, woven.
It's okay!
Oh!
Oh, man!
Oh, my God!
The back is amazing.
It's so cute.
It's true. It's cute.
Amazing.
That's Kazumi.
You drew it.
She's amazing.
And she's wearing a crown.
It's true.
She's wearing a lion's crown.
It's amazing.
A lot of love.
A cute lion.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Today is the day we are going to shoot the goods for the collaboration between Nearly Goal Joy and Spinz.
Thank you so much for the surprise announcement the other day, and today is the day of the photo shoot, so they've set the place up really nicely.
I'm wearing a black collaboration T-shirt.
I'm so happy to finally be able to wear it by myself for the first time, and there are many other items that you won't be able to see today.
I'm sure you'll be able to see something you don't normally see from the other members, so please enjoy the show and be sure to get your hands on one!
I usually do fresh photos of the idol Aimi Ozawa, but today I'm going to do a photo shoot with Mr. Spindo,
But today, I'm going to show you a picture of Spindo, so I'm not trying to look like an idol, Today is Spindo's day, so I'm not trying to be fancy,
I wanted to do something different from the raw photos,
What's that?
You're elaborating now, aren't you?
It's cute.
They were taken with very nice and stylish lights.
I am very grateful for that.
I hope you will be able to pick up a copy in the future.
Thank you.
Yay!
Hey!
I am very happy to be able to wear a knit hat for the first time in my life.
I hope I can show you all a different me from usual.
The hat is big.
Cute?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I will do my best after this. Thank you very much.
I wore this parka and scajan,
I'm really happy that you put together such a stylish coordination.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I can feel your back.
I'm glad you're here.
Exalted and lionized.
It's like a combination.
Very cool.
I'll do my best. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This is the first time since I became Joe that I'm wearing something different from the usual.
I'm wearing this scajan.
I think it looks really cool when worn alone.
but with the skirt and the ribbon, it has a little bit of cuteness to it.
I was able to take a pictureI was able to take pictures
I had a lot of help and encouragement from everyone.
It was the first time for me to do a photo shoot while showing my clothes.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it was. Oh, no.
There was a different person?
He's so cute.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
He's so cute.
Thank you so much.
It was really fun, and this costume is actually for sale,
I really enjoyed shooting this costume, which is actually for sale, because it has a very cute, loose-fitting feel to it,
I had a lot of fun taking pictures with that feeling,
I am really looking forward to seeing the clothes being sold to everyone,
I'm really looking forward to it.
What?
Thank you!
Thank you so much for your hard work!
It's soooo something.
She's so cute.
The clothes...
This is probably for real.
I might wear this all the time if it goes on sale.
I might get the whole set and wear it as is.
The photo shoot was also a little...
It's different from what I usually do.
It's different from the detergent shoot.
There are a lot of interesting poses
I had a lot of fun.
It was fun because it was free.
I'm glad you liked it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thanks for your time.
I'm Oomano, and it's nice to meet you.
It was really cute, and I had seen it in person when I first heard about it, but when I actually put the sleeves on, it was even cuter,
The photos were taken very nicely and styled beautifully, so I'm looking forward to seeing the photos,
I'm looking forward to seeing the pictures, and the goods that the other members are wearing are also very cute,
I'm very excited to think that these products will be delivered to you all. I am also looking forward to wearing them as much as possible.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
Looks difficult!
Suka-chan looks like she's wearing a uniform too.
Looks like she's wearing a uniform.
It's all so fresh.
We used a lot of curtains.
And we used a lot of curtains.
And this Suka-chan
with these girly outfits.
I realized that these skirts match with these girly outfits so well.
It was so fresh and fun.
It's a little bit crazy.
No, no, no.
I'm playing a different game.
But it's there.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to do some poses that are different from the poses that I usually do for the live photos and the merchandise and the potential photos.
I posed in a way to show off my clothes.
I posed a little bit like an energetic child, and I did my hair differently.
I also had my hair done in a different way than usual.
I got a lot of comments about how cute I was.
It was a really fun shoot!
Thank you very much.
This was the first time for us to collaborate on a product, and we were actually photographed as models,
I think you will be able to see a different side of us, with makeup and outfits that suit each of us,
I hope you all look forward to it.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Best regards.
Thank you very much.
Oh! Cute!
Cute!
Adorable!
So cute!
We had a great time shooting with everyone in Miyagi on the authentic set.
We had a great time shooting with everyone at Miyagi!
Thank you so much!
I tried a lot of poses and stuff.
I can't wait to see how it will turn out.
I'm looking forward to seeing how it will turn out!
I was asked to wear a dumpling.
I don't do that very often.
I think you'll be able to see a different side of me.
The collaboration with Spinz that we shot today will be on sale from January 13th.
It will go on sale on January 13th!
It's amazing!
It has the word "Joy" on it.
and it's so cute!
so be sure to look out for it!
Please check it out!
Thank you very much!
What's inside the toy?
What's inside the toy is..,
What's in the toy?
What's in the toy? What's in the toy,
What's in the toy is in the toy,
Thank you so much for shooting today.
This was our first collaboration, and I am very grateful,
I am also very happy that the set, costumes, hair and makeup were done so beautifully today.
We will do our best to promote the event and acquire a lot of experience so that many people will be able to get it.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.